<xml id="profileXML">
    <%= require('./parts/header-meta.xml') %>
    <projects>
        <!--Gvbvdxx's Scratch project archive-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbvdxx's Scratch project archive</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/scratch-archive.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>after-ban</tag>
                <tag>ban</tag>
                <tag>after</tag>
                <tag>archive</tag>
                <tag>scratch</tag>
                <tag>sb3</tag>
                <tag>blocked</tag>
                <tag>after-block</tag>
                <tag>after-blocked</tag>
                <tag>scratch blocked</tag>
                <tag>gvbvdxx</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              An full archive of all my <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu" target="_blank">Scratch</a> projects, including the alt accounts as well!<br/>

              Even has the famous "Scratch Sonic engine", which was used for some Sonic fangames on Scratch<br/>

              Load the SB3 files on the <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu/projects/editor" target="_blank">Scratch project editor</a> or inside <a href="https://turbowarp.org" target="_blank">Turbowarp</a>.

            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://gvbvdxx.itch.io/archive"
                >🎮 Itch.io</l>
                <l goto="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1l0u70F4CqF_ndKYMYE6lb1rSgkNHILKb"
                >📁 Google Drive direct link</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--Random Rants +-->
        <project>
            <label>Random Rants +</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/randomrants-plus.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>conversation</tag>
                <tag>rant</tag>
                <tag>site</tag>
                <tag>chill</tag>
                <tag>soundboard</tag>
                <tag>realtime</tag>
                <tag>webrtc</tag>
                <tag>websockets</tag>
                <tag>javascript</tag>
                <tag>accounts</tag>
                <tag>hangout</tag>
                <tag>school</tag>
                <tag>meme</tag>
                <tag>memes</tag>
                <tag>funny</tag>
                <tag>chromebooks</tag>
                <tag>school internet</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              This site I had made with and for a friend by sharing a Google
              Document to plan ideas on. It was meant to let us communicate
              better at school, but it has turned into a fully functional app
              you can use right here on gvbvdxx.me! This is a final version of
              the many "Prototypes" of different experiment versions I made.
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://randomrants-plus.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
                <l goto="https://randomrants-plus.onrender.com"
                >OnRender.com version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/ggm3-logo.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>ggm3</tag>
                <tag>game maker</tag>
                <tag>game tool</tag>
                <tag>games</tag>
                <tag>coding</tag>
                <tag>programming</tag>
                <tag>blockly</tag>
                <tag>scratch</tag>
                <tag>blocks</tag>
                <tag>video game</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              A online tool that lets you make games easily by using Blockly coding.
			  Inspired by 
                <a href="https://scratcm.mit.edu/projects/editor" target="_blank">Scratch</a>, 
                <a href="https://turbowarp.org" target="_blank">TurboWarp</a>, and the previous mod attempt called "Gvbvdxx Mod 2".
			  This online tool is still in the beta phase, so expect it to crash sometimes.
            
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://ggm3.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
                <l goto="https://ggm3-y1xs.onrender.com"
                >OnRender.com version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--Gvbvdxx Game Maker-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbvdxx Game Maker</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/ggm-logo.svg"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>ggm</tag>
                <tag>game maker</tag>
                <tag>game tool</tag>
                <tag>games</tag>
                <tag>coding</tag>
                <tag>programming</tag>
                <tag>blockly</tag>
                <tag>scratch</tag>
                <tag>blocks</tag>
                <tag>video game</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              A online tool that lets you make games easily.
			  The very first version of the Gvbvdxx Game Maker series.
			  This editor uses very outdated code, so you may see some bugs that aren't intended.
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://ggm.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--Gvbsonic-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbsonic (Gvbvdxx Sonic Engine)</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/gvbsonic-logo.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>sonic the hedgehog</tag>
                <tag>game</tag>
                <tag>games</tag>
                <tag>video game</tag>
                <tag>engine</tag>
                <tag>physics</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              A attempt to make Classic Sonic physics work directly in JavaScript,
			  this engine was inspired by my previous Scratch Classic Sonic physics projects.
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://gvbsonic.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--GvbvdxxScriptMaker-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbvdxx Script Maker</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/gvbvdxx-script-maker.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>blockly</tag>
                <tag>tool</tag>
                <tag>JavaScript</tag>
                <tag>coding</tag>
                <tag>programming</tag>
                <tag>transpiler</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              Gvbvdxx Script Maker is a tool to help people learn about JavaScript, just like I did.
                <br/>
              It lets you turn Scratch style code into code to be used with actual websites.
                <br/>
              This site was created during COVID years and during online school.
                <br/>
              There is no official logo from the time it was made for this site.
            
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://maker.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--Gvbvdxx Games-->
        <project>
            <label>Gvbvdxx Games</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/gvbvdxx-games-logo.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>scratch</tag>
                <tag>games</tag>
                <tag>video games</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              Gvbvdxx Games is a site that lets you play a few games that I've made on Scratch.
                <br/>
              These games are old, outdated, and very buggy, so you shouldn't treat them as "bad games", you should treat them as "pieces of gvbvdxx's history."
            
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://oldgames.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
        <!--SRB2 Web-->
        <project>
            <label>SRB2 Web</label>
            <thumbnail src="images/thumbnails/srb2web.png"/>
            <tags>
                <tag>browser</tag>
                <tag>port</tag>
                <tag>games</tag>
                <tag>video games</tag>
                <tag>srb2</tag>
                <tag>web</tag>
                <tag>multiplayer</tag>
                <tag>online multiplayer</tag>
                <tag>Sonic Robo Blast 2</tag>
            </tags>
            <description>
              An entire port of SRB2 to the web browser, the goal wasn't just to port it but also have completely working online multiplayer.
            </description>
            <links>
                <l goto="https://srb2web.gvbvdxx.me"
                >🌐 GVBVDXX.me version</l>
            </links>
        </project>
    </projects>
    <profile>
        <name>Gvbvdxx</name>
        <bg css="url('images/profile-bg.png') center/cover no-repeat"/>
        <pfp src="images/profile.png"/>
        <social>
            <l
              goto="https://youtube.com/@gvbvdxx"
              logo="images/socials/youtube.svg"
              label="Youtube"></l>
            <l
              goto="https://gvbvdxx.itch.io"
              logo="images/socials/itch-io.svg"
              label="Itch.io"
            ></l>
            <l
              goto="https://github.com/gvbvdxxalt2"
              logo="images/socials/github.svg"
              label="GitHub"
            ></l>
            <l
              goto="https://discord.com/users/1160668172228247623"
              logo="images/socials/discord.svg"
              label="Discord"
            ></l>
        </social>
        <stories>
            <story default label="🌐 Welcome!">
                <h2>Welcome to my domain!</h2>
				  I'm a high school student.
                
                <br/>
		          I build websites &amp; video games for friends, for fun, and the public using JavaScript or webpack,
		          I can also build servers using Node.JS.

                <br/>
                    ❤🌐 I love the internet as well!
                
                <br/>
				  Also known as "Jason Glen Evans"
                
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <b>You can interact with the tabs above to read my different pages.</b>
            </story>
            <story label="📜 More about me">
                <h2>Who am I?</h2>
                <p>I'm Gvbvdxx, my username came from kid me pressing random buttons on the keyboard when I started using 
                
                    <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu" target="_blank">Scratch</a>, the username has stuck with me ever since, even after I was banned.
					You can also call me by the first 3 letters of my username (my friends prefer this online), or just call me "Jason".
                </p>
                <h2>What do I make?</h2>
                <p>I make various websites, I'm very good at JavaScript, now using Webpack. I like real time sites the most since you can interact with other people.
                
                    <br/>
					I also like writing games on sites and other places but it's extremely difficult to debug or make them when I'm grounded because of Chromebook restrictions.
                </p>
                <h2>What is this domain for?</h2>
                <p>This domain hopefully would stay up, and be used to share my projects on. Currently right now it's still being updated.
                
                    <br/>
					If you're seeing issues with the domain, don't panic, its part of the process of me learning how to make the domain work.
                </p>
                <p>Bookmark the URL in the "🛜 Domain Uptime" tab, you can use it to determine if the site is down only for you.</p>
                <br/>
            </story>
            <story label="🟢 Current status">
                <h2>🟢 Current status</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>Current development device</b>: Chromebook survival mode (Grounded for more than 2 years)
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>Current inerest(s)</b>: Designing a website domain
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🤪 ADHD</b>: 100%
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🧠 Autism</b>: Probably, the doctor says that "I'm on the spectrum." 🧑‍⚕ I'm going to get testing. 
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🧑‍🏫 School Grade</b>: 9th
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🎂 Birthday</b>: September 30th, 2010 (🧮 You do the age calcuations!)
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🕒 Time zone</b>: (UTC-4:00) Eastern Daylight Time (New York)
                    
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </story>
            <story label="📚 Grades">
                <h2>📚 Grades</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>📖 English</b>: 63%
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🏃 Gym/PE</b>: 89%
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>🔢 Math</b>: 65%
                    
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>📜 History</b>: 92%
                    
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </story>
            <story label="💻 Internet Filters ❌">
                <p>
				  These are the "Boss Battles" of my school internet:
                    <br/>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>🌐 Internet Level</b>: Cisco Umbrella. (Easiest to code on)
	                    
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <b>💻 Laptop/Chromebook Level</b>: Lightspeed Filter Agent, Lightspeed Insight Agent. (The "Cat Mario" level stuff)
	                    
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            </story>
            <story label="🛜 Domain Uptime">
                <p>Domain uptime is located 
                    <a href="https://stats.uptimerobot.com/a0xrFFxOH1" target="_blank">here.</a>
                </p>
                <p>I use Github Pages, Cloudflare, and NameCheap to power these domains, additionally I use 
                    <a href="https://render.com" target="_">render.com</a> to power any Node.JS servers I've made.
                </p>
            </story>
            <story label="🧑‍💻🐙 Source Code">
                <p>
				  This site is 100% open source, 
                    <a href="https://github.com/gvbvdxxalt2/gvbvdxx.me" target="_blank">click here to see it!</a>
                </p>
            </story>
            <story label="🤖 How I use AI">
                <h2>🤖 How I use AI</h2>
                <p>
					Many people might be concerned that I'm now using AI to code.
                    <br/>
                    <b>I DON'T</b> use AI to generate entire sites (without notice), but I do use it to research, generate some UI text, generate legal text, verify if the content is good for my users, simplify JavaScript library Wikis, generate code for programming languages I don't know how to use, write code that I can't easily learn by myself, optimize or organize code, and also fix bugs that I don't know how to fix.
                    <br/>
					If I do use AI, I usually have to debug it a lot, so if you think I completley forgot how to code, I did not, I still have to put effort into making sure it works, and suggesting my own ideas to fix it.
					Here is some code that I used AI to make:
					
                    <ul>
                        <li>Pixel collision detectors - This is used in Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3, JSIfy (Scratch To JavaScript), and maybe some other games and other apps.</li>
                        <li>Some portions of Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3 - Used to organize some of Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3's code, implement block copying to other sprites by dragging them onto sprites, and also add the red outline to blocks for code errors.</li>
                        <li>WebGL rendering - This is extremely complex, but I used a JavaScript library to simplify it, but it wasn't enough so I had to use AI and the library, Gvbvdxx Game Maker 3 uses both.</li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            </story>
            <story label="😾🔨 Scratch History (🤖💬 AI short version)">
                <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu" target="_blank">Don't know what Scratch is? Click here.</a>
                <h2>🐱 The Start &amp; The First Reports</h2>
                <p>I started young on an off-brand desktop, building cloud games to feel connected. I built a numeric encoder/decoder to allow chat—something Scratch forbids. I didn't get the rules yet; I just wanted to build cool things. This led to my first "inappropriate" flags and reports.</p>
                <h2>🧑‍💻 Programmer Life &amp; The Hacking Lesson</h2>
                <p>In 2018, I found a 
                    
                    <i>Bad Piggies</i> disc with an 
                    
                    <b>HTA file</b>. Messing with that JS led me to modern web tools. During COVID, I used 
                    
                    <b>Blockly</b> and 
                    
                    <b>Node.JS</b> to build real-time chats while "attending" school. My first site was hacked via an 
                    
                    <code>innerHTML</code> attack by 
                    
                    <i>user123</i>, which taught me more about security in 48 hours than two years of casual coding.
                
                </p>
                <h2>🪦 Life Flips &amp; Uncle Awareness</h2>
                <p>After losing my dad, my uncle moved in and grounded me, throwing my setup into storage. My room became a "depression space," leading to a 
                    
                    <b>"Tom and Jerry"</b> war. I found "holes" in his rules by using school Chromebooks and hidden laptops to keep coding.
                
                </p>
                <h2>🤖 The Bot &amp; The Permanent Ban</h2>
                <p>I built a 
                    
                    <b>"Scratch Guest Commenter"</b> bot using a Node.JS API. I thought I was a hero, but people used it to spam. Scratch blamed me for the bot's actions and issued a permanent block. The appeal was denied with a final: 
                    
                    <i>"Do not make any further appeals."</i>
                </p>
                <h2>😾🔨 The Scratch Rebellion</h2>
                <p>I couldn't let go. I made an alias, 
                    
                    <i>onehopthistime</i>, remaking "bad" projects with better physics. I deleted it to avoid an 
                    
                    <b>identity crisis</b>, then tried again to promote 
                    
                    <b>Gvbvdxx Mod 2</b> (a duct-tape patch version with TurboWarp extensions). I was banned again and again.
                
                </p>
                <h2>📡 The Final Cycle &amp; IP Bans</h2>
                <p>In a final attempt, I used Node.JS to cycle through multiple accounts to promote my safer chat sites. It backfired: people accused my URLs of being 
                    
                    <b>"cookie loggers,"</b> and I ended up getting the entire 
                    
                    <b>Codesandbox IP banned</b>. This probably is the end... but who knows, there could be more!
                
                </p>
            </story>
            <story label="😾🔨 Scratch ban history (📖 Long version)">
                <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu" target="_blank">Don't know what Scratch is? Click here.</a>
                <br/>
                <h2>🐱 The start</h2>
                <p>I started out without a 
                
                    <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu" target="_blank">Scratch</a> account, I used to make projects on my slow off-brand desktop computer or some slow laptop when I was younger.
					Everything was fine, I was creating different projects and games, just doing my thing.
					So I started to make a cloud game because when I was playing other cloud games, I felt like I was involved with the community in real time.
                </p>
                <h2>⚠ First few reports</h2>
                <p>I started out following griffpatch's tutorials and eventually made my own, this project eventually became "GSE Sonic cloud", it offered one thing Scratch hates, cloud chat. However, the cloud chat in the game wasn't what got me in trouble.
					I didn't know chat wasn't allowed in Scratch, but every time I loaded the project, it risked freezing my laptop or desktop, so if I just wanted to have an conversation, It would cost me Out of Memory errors or cause my slow Chromebook laptop to black screen and restart.
					To fix this, I made a project, just the bare minimum, for a cloud chat, an numeric encoder (since Scratch doesn't let you store text), and a numeric decoder, and a List variable that is displayed. Once this was complete I shared the project and invited people, eventually people liked it, but there was this one person.
					This person joined the chat, and said "I don't think this project is allowed", and next thing I knew the project and my mail had said "This project is inappropiate for Scratch". I was confused, so I made a studio announcement (I like to do these a lot), and people said "You're breaking the rules".</p>
					I didn't truly get them, just thinking they're mean, but I stayed happy after that and continued my other project creations.
					
					
                
                <h2>🧑‍💻 Programmer life</h2>
                <p>Later in my life, I discovered JavaScript (in 2018-ish), and all the other web tools, how? Their was this PC game disc my parents decided to buy from Ebay (which was 🐷Bad Piggies! a game I liked since I was a baby), it had a HTA file, and when it said "Autoplay" on the computer, it opened the HTA file, with a fancy image window with an "Install" button.
					I messed with the HTA file using some outdated old JavaScript, and eventually I got onto searching for help on the internet using W3Schools and all the other good stuff. Eventually this moved into modern Chrome that I had installed on my computer.</p>
                <p>Eventually I got into the COVID-19 era (2020), everyone was online school, and eventually I figured out that by putting the "meet" tab to the left or minimizing it could let the teacher "think" im there, but I could be making A site instead! So what was I making? I figured out this site called "Blockly", and it was a Google Demo that had let you experiment with the Blockly workspace, I used this to learn javascript, and eventually followed the tutorials to make "Gvbvdxx's Script Maker", I added my own blocks, and somewhat still exists on github pages. I even shared this on Scratch discussion forms, letting everyone post their "XML" codes to share their scripts they created!</p>
                <p>I was wondering, "Since this is so powerful, I could make a conversation site!", and searched up on the internet, "How to make a chat site in JavaScript", eventually lead me to this tutorial showing how to use Socket.io to mirror messages and echo them out to all clients, and showed how to receive and send them through the JavaScript site.</p>
                <h2>💬 First real time site</h2>
                <p>Eventually I made a working site, this site was pretty basic, it said "Chat by Gvbvdxx" on the top of the page, and in the middle there was a "disabled" property "textarea", and at the bottom there was an "text input", with an "send" button. Before this screen there was an "home" screen, where you can customize your name, and click "join", there was no duplicate username checks, it still had the "Chat by Gvbvdxx" on the top. Just the bare minimum for a chat site.
					However, it still was a prototype on my computer, I knew I could upload on Github Pages, but I still needed a server, many people would probably port forward, but I didn't want to waste electricity on "port forwarding a server", plus I didn't know how to turn the websockets into "WSS", so I searched "How to make a websocket server public", clicked the "videos" tab, scrolled through, and found this guy which was on Glitch.com.</p>
                <p>Got the server to be up, but this was made using the "ws" module, and not "Socket.io", but I didn't know, and really didn't care, since it just "worked". It was a small and extremely simple script. Just "when I recieve a message from anyone, send the message out to everyone connected to the server."</p>
                <p>This was convient, but very easy to use against people who were actually using it for good things, but like I said, I didn't know yet, and I had no ideas with "server security" even was.
					Of coure you guessed, I shared this with everyone on Scratch who followed me, and also made a "studio annocument" on Scratch with the link to the github pages site.</p>
                <p>Eventually one showed up, and said "yo, this is cool!", and this is where everything "clicked," a thousand times of boost of motivation flew into me, and this was the best site to me, and then people joined, it turned into "Basic site", to a full "app", it wasn't fully complete compared to actual "chat apps", but it had eveything a "rule-unknown Scratcher" would like, at this point the site moved from "basic site", to a site with styled messages using real Div elements and stuff instead of textareas, this is also how the "Profile pictures" were added, even I added something special "of my own", letting people pick their "username color".</p>
                <h2>🥲 The first incident</h2>
                <p>One day, when I wasn't on the site, somone appeared in my mail on my profile saying "Somone is taking over your site, their posting (weird thing) pictures", so I knew I had to do something.</p>
                <p>So I joined the chat, and then this person who was "taking over the site", rejoined with my name, everyone was trying to lag him out by "spamming", but he claimed "I have opera GX", eventually that didn't work, saw what "pictures" he was posting, and I was thinking "I need a way to ban him", so then I was making a "ban system", however this was the most basic way possible, just add an "IP" property to the messages by using a API to get "IP", monitor the echos with a websocket test site, and add a message to "ban" with the IP, I thought this was bulletproof, but it wasn't.
					The guy was gone for a second, but then he rejoined, and stepped it up even more, eventually the site was redirecting to "google" weirdly, but I just thought it was a bug. Eventually the site turned red and sayed "Hacked By user123" on the top left and was sliding around the screen from left to right, apparently this was an "innerHTML" attack, like I said, I didn't really know that it was insecure, I thought "this is a way to put text", and I just used "innerHTML" to set the content, which turned into him using bad image paths and attaching to the onerror to run JavaScript without prompting, and also was leaking everyone's IPs, I was pretty much facing the worst, but I was 50% scared, like angry and threatened at the same time.</p>
                <p>Eventually everone was scared out and left but me, eventually he said "You need to make this site more secure", and left.
					I thought this was the end but it wasn't.</p>
                <h2>😦 The first scratch ban 🔨</h2>
                <p>When I went back to Scratch to work on my favorite projects, it said "Account blocked", however this was temporary, it said "Do not post or discuss about unmoderated chat links" or similar, and had a timer.
					I just thought "my site IS moderated, I have a ban system in place, so people couldn't abuse it", completley thinking that "user123" was just hacking into the ban system.</p>
                <p>So when I got allowed back onto Scratch, it was pure "unknowingly rebelling", I shared the site again and again, doing the studio invites again, eventually I started gaining "haters" that kept saying "don't follow this guy, he would spam studio invites".
					I still ignored them, and just kept on doing what made me happy, I kept meeting people and eventually I started making "online friends".</p>
                <h2>🪦 Life flips upside down</h2>
                <p>This is where everything turned upside down on me. One day I woke up (in 2021 or 2022ish I think), and my grandparents said (I live with them), "your dad is in trouble, he is at the hospital", and the next day my grandparents announced "your dad is gone."
					Eventually online school has ended and I was officially now going to 6th grade, my uncle starts going to my house and eventually, he has officially moved in.</p>
                <H2>⏪ A quick rewind</H2>
                <p>Before 6th grade starts, I was still communicating using the chat app, and met a person called MiniScratchGamer, eventually we became "online friends", when I checked my profile, someone said "join (a kosmi link) you should try it", and this is when I officially tried Kosmi, and then this was my main app.
					I started inviting people to that app, and eventually I had a friend list, now I could litterally just click a button to bring them in, but Scratch still "hated" me.</p>
                <p>One day, MiniScratchGamer said, "you're so popular, I need to know what it feels like to be popular", and asked me for a password, I said no a few times, but he kept begging, this is also to mention there was someone else in the room, and I tried giving it away with "hints", but eventually I gave up and gave him it, I was going to change it later, but at this point I forgot it happend, and when I said the password, the other guy in the room was like "NOOO! 😭", and Immediatley (and weirdly) the account was banned immediatley for "password sharing", which made me wonder "Is Scratch silently watching me?".
					Also during this time, I was creating a Scratch modification called Gvbvdxx Mod, which actually made me "Slightly more popular".</p>
                <h2>🔨😾 Even more bans</h2>
                <p>This is the "best of the worst", since I was still unknowingly rebelling Scratch, I still kept getting the timeout bans, eventually I even started appealing to them, eventually I said to myself "I'm doing wrong", and sent out my final appeal.
					The Scratch team accepted, and we "aggreed" not to try to do this again, but an entire new path to the final no-more-trust ban remains.</p>
                <h2>⚠ Uncle becomes aware</h2>
                <p>Fast forward to 6th grade:
					Every day at 6th grade has become another day for a zero grade, every minute, feels like a second, I was coding every time the teacher speaked, and every time I opened my Chromebook, the class noise slows down.</p>
                <p>Eventually, my uncle grounds me, he takes away the desktop power cable, and after a few weeks, he throws everything into a storage space somewhere in the world.
					My room has became from "full of coder space" into "full of depression space", except I hid a few laptops, this has officially came into a "war of coder vs grades" and a "tom and jerry" show with me and my uncle, I keep finding "holes" which are spots of computer time, and my uncle finds them out eventually and "patches them with tape" which means more grounding and measures.</p>
                <p>However, there is ONE thing he can't touch, my school chromebook, even if he takes mines, I still can rely on the "chromebook cart", just grab a chromebook from there, and boom, another perfect day of coding.</p>
                <h2>😾🔨 No more Scratch</h2>
                <p>I was bored one time, flipped open my Chromebook, and opened Glitch. And I was curious about the Scratch API.
					Eventually I ended up on NPM with a Scratch API Node JS module, opened it's source code, and decided to "use" it for a site.
					The site was an experiment, it first started out with my profile posting a "test" comment, and I ended up making an entirely new account for it, which was the bot account.
					Then I added cloud variables, made a project on my actual profile, and when people tried it, it would say their message using my bot account on their profile!</p>
                <p>I added an interface since nobody would use a buggy project to interface with the bot, and called it "Scratch Guest Commenter", I thought I was a hero for making this, letting any person not familliar with Scratch let them post "very good" comments on peoples Scratch profiles.
					I thought the Scratch moderation system was my friend now, and that it would be smart enough to beleive that other people on the experiment site was saying that, but actually it wasn't.</p>
                <p>This actually was the perfect "I say something bad, you get the blame for it" situation for the site, someone would say something bad, go to the bots profile, say "You gotta stop saying this", and report, and repeat, the bot was filling up with "Welcome back to Scratch!" messages from the scratch moderation system, and guess who got the blame, me. 
					There was also people warning me on my profile, saying "you should stop the bot account", but I didn't understand what they said, they're saying "something is happening to the bot account", but I hear "they probably just mean the app is breaking, let me check the logs".</p>
                <p>I also added a "ban screen" for the app, just in case it does get banned (because I was in a mixed feeling after seeing the notices), and tested it using my banned alt accounts, and then added the bot back to the site, this was just for if the bot account got banned, so people could see what's wrong.</p>
                <br/>
                <h2>😾 The final Scratch team message</h2>
                <p>One day, I checked my account, it said, "Account blocked", immediately panicked, and then was calm, because I remembered a tip, "Appeal to Scratch", so I did it.</p>
                <p>
                    <br/>After waiting a few weeks, I got this:
                
                    <br/>
                    <b style="color: orange;">Based on your last history on the Scratch website, your account will not be unblocked.
                    
                        <br/>Do not use or make any other Scratch accounts or send in any further appeals.
                    
                        <br/>You are welcome to use the offline editor to make projects: 
                    
                        <a href="https://scratch.mit.edu/download" target="_blank">https://scratch.mit.edu/download</a>
                    </b>
                    <br/>
					This is the official "We hate you now" from Scratch, but saying it in the nicest way possible.
                
                </p>
                <h2>😾🔨 Last moments of Scratch</h2>
                <p>Of course, I tried to persist in the "Scratch rebellion", this time knowing it was wrong but I still had "Scratch in heart", I made a new account, told everyone about it, and tried to get back again.
					The next day, got banned again, but this time I tried different, instead of saying, "It's me Gvbvdxx, I'm banned", I made a new name, called "onehopthistime", made some good "improvment projects" which were remixes of "bad" projects like flappy bird clones (which felt insanely snappy since it had poor code), and remade it with gravity and physics.
					I then noticed, if I kept making these projects and lying about who I am, I would get famous on another name, and then I would be in an "online identity crisis", so I "killed the account" (deleted the account), and stopped making it completley, but little did I know I would try again.</p>
                <p>The next time, I wanted to advertise a newer version of Gvbvdxx Mod, called Gvbvdxx Mod 2, which used TurboWarp, and also now included the new TurboWarp extension library.
					Gvbvdxx Mod 2 has existed for a while, and was already advertised on Scratch when I wasn't banned, but it didn't include my recent updates with the TurboWarp extensions, since it used a older version of TurboWarp.
					This new version was a "Ducktape patch", it did some weird but working code to install the extensions onto Gvbvdxx Mod 2.
          Of course, got banned again, and thought I'll truly give up this time.</p>
                <p>This time it was different, Instead of making one account, I made many accounts.
					These were different username scrambles, using different letters.
					And then I reused my "Scratch Comment" site to post comments, and added a cycling system to cycle through different comments, all written in Node.JS to "friendly bot" the site, going through follower lists on my profile, I used it to promote some of my newer and safer chat sites, but ended up getting the entire Codesandbox IP banned, and also getting blamed on making "cookie loggers" by putting the URLs to the site I wanted to promote.</p>
                <p>This probably is the end, but who knows, there could still be more!</p>
            </story>
        </stories>
    </profile>
</xml>
